{
  "decadeGameData": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Decade Trivia",
      "categories": [
        {
          "id": "1-1",
          "categorytitle": "1960s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "1-1-1",
              "question": "Who won the Best Picture at the Academy Awards in 1960?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "The Apartment"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-2",
              "question": "What was the name of the military conflict that the United States was involved in during the 1960s and 1970s?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "Vietnam War"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-3",
              "question": "Who was the first man to walk on the moon?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Neil Armstrong"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-4",
              "question": "Which famous music festival took place in upstate New York in 1969?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Woodstock"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-5",
              "question": "Which political leader was assassinated in Dallas, Texas, in 1963?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "John F. Kennedy"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-2",
          "categorytitle": "1970s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "2-2-1",
              "question": "Which actor played the iconic character Rocky Balboa in the film \"Rocky\" released in 1976?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Sylvester Stallone"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-2",
              "question": "What was the highest-grossing film of the 1970s?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Star Wars"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-3",
              "question": "Which American president resigned from office in 1974?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Richard Nixon"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-4",
              "question": "Which American serial killer terrorized California in the late 1960s and early 1970",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "The Zodiac Killer"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-5",
              "question": "Which disco hit by the Bee Gees was featured in the film \"Saturday Night Fever\" released in 1977?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Stayin' Alive"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-3",
          "categorytitle": "1980s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "3-3-1",
              "question": "Who was the first female British Prime Minister?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Margaret Thatcher"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-2",
              "question": "Which iconic handheld gaming device was released by Nintendo in 1989?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Game Boy"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-3",
              "question": "What was the highest-grossing film of the 1980s?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-4",
              "question": "Which famous album by Michael Jackson was released in 1982?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Thriller"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-5",
              "question": "What was the popular dance style that emerged in the 1980s known for its robotic movements",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "Breakdancing"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-4",
          "categorytitle": "1990s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "4-4-1",
              "question": "Which popular sitcom featured six friends living in New York City?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Friends"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-2",
              "question": "Which female artist released the hit song \"Baby One More Time\" in 1998?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Britney Spears"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-3",
              "question": "What was the name of the highest-grossing animated film of the 1990s?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "The Lion King"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-4",
              "question": "Which American president signed the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) into law in 1993?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Bill Clinton"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-5",
              "question": "What was the name of the conflict between Iraq and a coalition led by the United States in the early 1990s?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "Gulf War"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-5",
          "categorytitle": "2000s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "5-5-1",
              "question": "Which social media platform was founded by Mark Zuckerberg in 2004?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Facebook"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-2",
              "question": "What was the name of the first smartphone released by Apple in 2007?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "iPhone"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-3",
              "question": "Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor for his role in the film \"Ray\" released in 2004?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Jamie Foxx"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-4",
              "question": "Which country hosted the 2008 Summer Olympics?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "China"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-5",
              "question": "Which catastrophic hurricane struck the Gulf Coast of the United States in 2005?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "Hurricane Katrina"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}

